financially-blonde.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy Policy | Financially BlondeFinancially Blonde

**Financially Blonde, LLC Privacy Policy**

Financially Blonde, LLC (“Financially Blonde” or “our”, “us” or “we”) understands that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use [www.financially-blonde.com](http://www.financially-blonde.com/) or other websites owned or operated by Financially Blonde (collectively or individually “Users” or “you”) value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Website (as hereinafter defined). Financially Blonde provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Website.

**Effective Date.**

The most recent version of this Privacy Policy is effective as of August 12, 2013.

**Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy applies to www.financially-blonde.com and/or other affiliated websites or entities controlled by, or under common control with and through Financially Blonde (each such website being individually referred to herein as the “Website”). Financially Blonde respects the privacy of its users, and this Privacy Policy details the information that is collected on its Website and how such information is used by Financially Blonde. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review the [Terms of Use](http://financially-blonde.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms Of Use") posted at our Website, which governs your use of the Website. Your use of the Website indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy and in the Terms of Use Finally your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Applicability.**

This Privacy Policy only applies to websites owned and/or operated by or for Financially Blonde, and upon which Financially Blonde has placed a “link” which, when “clicked”, transfers you to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at this Website, and does not cover any information collected by any other website (unless otherwise specifically stated or disclosed by Financially Blonde), its corporate affiliates, licensees or any other company, regardless of whether you used a link on the Website to click through to a third party website.

**Disclosure of Information.**

  1. Personally Identifiable Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, birth date or e-mail address and referred to in this Privacy Policy as “PII”) to Financially Blonde when choosing to participate in various activities on the Website such as uploading videos, posting reviews in our forums, message board, or in the video comments section if applicable, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. Generally, you may browse our Website without providing us with PII. However, there may be times when we ask you to provide us with certain PII, such as when you choose to register with our Website. We may also ask you to provide us with demographic information or information regarding your interests, hobbies or similar information to enhance your online experience. Financially Blonde reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or add features to our Website that require you to register or otherwise provide additional PII or to require registration to access the Website. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to participate in or view some of the Website’s features. Financially Blonde does not sell, rent or share PII collected with other people other than that specifically described herein.

  2. Underage users: The Website does not knowingly collect PII from children under eighteen (18) years of age. This is not a Website directed to children under the age of 18. If you are under 18 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to Financially Blonde. If we discover that a child under the age of 18 has provided the Website with PII, we will delete that child’s PII from its system.

  3. Anonymous Information: When you visit the Website, our web servers automatically collect website usage information. Website usage information is anonymous information that describes how our visitors use and navigate our Website, and it includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, video and the time-span of their stays. Financially Blonde collects the anonymous information automatically sent to us by your web browser, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Website, and IP address. We may also determine what technology is available through your browser in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page.

  4. Log File Information: When visitors call for pages from our Website, our servers log the visitor’s IP address. Financially Blonde may collect IP addresses for a range of internal purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to review the number of visits to different pages or videos watched on our Website.

  5. Cookies Information: When you visit the Website, Financially Blonde may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Financially Blonde does not store any PII in cookies, but it may link the cookie to any information it collects. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers, which is standard in the Internet industry. Financially Blonde does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our Privacy Policy. Visitors to our Website should check the Privacy Policy of the advertiser to determine how it uses cookies. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of our Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

  6. Clear GIFs Information: When you use the Website, Financially Blonde may employ “clear GIFs” which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

**Use of Information.**

  1. If you submit PII to Financially Blonde through the Website, then we may employ your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Website. We may also use your PII to contact you regarding your use of our Website or changes to our Privacy Policy or other notices or terms that affect you and your use of our Website. If you e-mail someone else a review or other special feature from the Website, Financially Blonde may use the information you provide about someone else to send that person the requested e-mail.

  2. Any PII or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

  3. Financially Blonde may not use your email address or other PII to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Website changes or for customer service purposes).

  4. Financially Blonde may use both your PII and certain non-personally-identifiable information to improve the quality and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

  5. Financially Blonde may use cookies, clear gifs, and log file PII to: (a) retain information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (b) supply custom, personalized content and information; (c) examine the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

  6. Financially Blonde may employ other trusted companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. Such third parties may have access to our Users’ PII in order to provide these services to us on our behalf solely for such purposes; however, they are not permitted to use it for any other purpose.

  7. Financially Blonde may not rent, sell or otherwise disclose your PII to third parties unless disclosed herein or at the time such information is collected or unless you otherwise give consent, other than in the following limited circumstances:

    1. Legal Action: Financially Blonde may disclose information about its users, including PII, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Website and applicable state and federal laws, or to protest against misuse or unauthorized use of the Website. We may also disclose user PII whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability, to protect or defend our rights or property or protect the safety, rights or property of our users. We also reserve the right to disclose PII and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Financially Blonde believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use.

    2. Corporate Change: Financially Blonde may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose user information, including PII, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other fundamental corporate change respecting the Website.

**Security.**

  1. You may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Website, in which case Financially Blonde may not be able to provide certain services to you. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the Website cannot be removed and remain subject to the Terms of Use.

  2. Financially Blonde takes steps to secure the data you submit to us, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our user data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be one hundred percent secure. Therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Financially Blonde, and you do so at your own risk.

**Consent to Transfer.**

The Website is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and the Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**Acceptance/Changes to Privacy Policy**

By using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Financially Blonde reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion. We will post any changes here; therefore, please continue to check back from time to time. However, we will only use the PII you provide to the Website in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, unless you give us your consent.

**Third-party Advertisers.**

  1. Financially Blonde permits other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to deliver advertisements within the Website. They may also use other tools to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content.

  2. As noted above, Financially Blonde does not provide any PII to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if Financially Blonde is requested by an advertiser to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may determine that you fit the profile of the audience it is trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Website, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any PII), to calculate which ads it should send to you.

  3. If you are concerned with the use of your non-personal information by these third party advertisers, you should consult their respective privacy policies for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Financially Blonde’s Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the address provided on the Website from which you “clicked” via an authorized link to arrive at this Privacy Policy. If you’d like to contact us about our Privacy Policy, please email us at: info@finblonde.com.

Shannon is a financial planner who left a "traditional" financial services firm to start her own company, NextGen Financial, because she felt traditional financial services firms did not have the tools or resources to help people in their 20s and 30s who are starting out and trying to build assets while also managing debt. She realized that the key to long term personal financial success is a commitment to financial fitness and making smart financial choices. Through this blog, her books and her company, Shannon is committed to making financial fitness fun, easy and accessible for others.
